

# SITI NUR INSYIRAH BINTI SHAUKI

ANALYST PROGRAMMER

#### **PROFILE**

Analyst Programmer with 2 years' experience in Dagangnet Technologies Sdn Bhd and an extensive range of skills including programming, and reporting. Strongly focused with ability to complete tasks accurately in a fast-faced environment with conflicting deadlines.

#### **CONTACT**

PHONE:

014-7370966

**EMAIL:** 

sitiinsyirah161296@gmail.com

Github:

https://github.com/syirahshauki1612 96

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Universiti Tenaga Nasional (UNITEN)**

2015 - 2018

Bachelor of Computer Science (Software Engineering) (Hons.)

CGPA: 3.32

#### **Universiti Tenaga Nasional (UNITEN)**

2014 - 2015

Foundation in Computer Science

CGPA: 3.60

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Dagangnet Technologies Sdn Bhd (Analyst Programmer) OCT 2018-OCT 2020

- Analyze application requirements and design specifications for the development of new applications or enhancement of existing applications.
- Code, debug and test developed applications.
- Work closely with testing teams in ensuring that the application meets the requirements that were specified by clients/users.
- Create web application that enable user to be registered online, while officer can verify and approve user of applications.

#### Dagangnet Technologies Sdn Bhd (Internship Student) FEB 2018-SEP 2018

• Code, debug and test developed applications

## **SKILLS**

